I got an offer on my place.
We could start over, find our style as a couple.
If I move, how do I know I'll be happy there?
Sounds like our mothers had a few things in common.
- Tell me more. - Let's just say she did a number on me.
My husband ran a few businesses in the Arconia, and Lester worked for him.
Lester didn't wanna tell me much about what he did.
He didn't feel good about the job.
But you think somebody killed my husband?
- Could I take you out to dinner? - I have no evidence
that you're actually a good guy.
We're just a bunch of rich people hashing out a bet.
The same one we were trying to settle the last time we were in that gaming parlor.
The night your doorman died, we played for a very big contract.
One of you is planning to build New York City's first casino.
I think I'll start renovations with... Oliver's apartment.
What are you talking about?
That offer on your place was from me.
I'm the one buying up all the apartments here.
You're turning The Arconia into a casino? All in.
For thousands of years, men have sung about luck being a lady.
In Carmina Burana, Carl Orff obsesses over Fortuna, the goddess of fortune.
Frank Sinatra prayed for luck to be a lady,
but still worried she'd go "blow on some other guy's dice."
Men love to blame anything in their life that they can't control... their bad luck,
on ladies.
Listen, you animals, next round is on me, alright?
As long as the scotch isn't old enough to be kissed, or drafted.
Uh-oh.
Queen of Decor has noticed my cracked leather.
Worst day of my life.
Adds character.
You're just being sweet.
Ah, this place has seen better days. Hey, get lost.
I know what she likes.
Interested in a makeover?
- What are you thinking? Uh, bangs or a shag? - For the casino, you goof.
I could help. Give it a woman's touch.
Ooh, what about this idea?
Let me host a private Ladies' Night in here. Once a month.
A night without cigars... or loud men hitting on us.
Done. I love ladies.
But don't worry, I never hit on 'em unless they want me to.
- And if they want you to? - Well, then, I make 'em a drink.
We have to move out because of a casino?!
Do you remember what I had to do to hold onto my apartment?
I burned a man.
I set fire to a dear friend! Plus, I bought a Peloton.
- Hey! - Hi!
Look at this cute place.
Oh, I'm taking a dance cardio class,
and we're using one of your songs for a routine.
I would show it to you, but it's got a lot of thrusting.
- It's not appropriate for a lady. - Unnecessary.
Mabitita, my new old friend,
I got you and however many plus-ones you want
tickets to a party tonight.
I'd totally come with, but we both know I'd just get drunk,
and tomorrow I'm in a music video where I have to operate heavy machinery, so...
Thank you so much. I just-- I have a lot of case stuff.
No, chica, this is case stuff. It's an impossible invite to get.
It's a Ladies' Night for important ladies like moi,
and it's literally in the building.
You get in through like-- like a closet or something,
sort of like a speakeasy. Ooh-la-la.
What? But Nicky's dead. Wait, who's throwing this party?